Once Upon a Prince is a tv movie, romance film directed by Alex Wright.
Susanna gladly accepts help one day from handsome stranger Nate at
her parents’ garden store in small-town Georgia.
Sparks between them fly, but when a photo of them gets leaked to the press, Susanna is in for the shock of her life
when Nate is called back home by his mother… For his coronation as the King Nathaniel of Cambria!
Susanna Truit, played by Megan Park.
Nate, played by Jonathan Keltz.
The Queen, played by Sara Botsford.
Mrs. June Waller, played by Colleen Winton.
Avery Truit, played by Kayla Wallace.
John, played by Charles Jarman.
Once Upon a Time in Venice is a 2017 American crime comedy film directed by Mark
Cullen in his directorial debut, who co-wrote with his brother Robb.
The film stars Bruce Willis, Jason Momoa, John Goodman, Thomas
Middleditch, Famke Janssen, Adam Goldberg, and Jessica Gomes.
The film follows private detective Steve Ford (Willis) and his assistant (Middleditch) as they face
many tasks, notably the capture of Ford's dog by a gang leader named Spyder (Momoa).
Once Upon a Time in Venice was released in a limited theatrical release and
through video on demand on June 16, 2017, by RLJ Entertainment.
The film received negative reviews from critics.
The tone is emotional.